quickweb.co.nz 2018-12-21

# QuickWeb - Terms of Service (Tos)

We respect your right to privacy and support the recently introduced General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) enforced on 25th May 2018. In the following sections we will cover which data we collect, how that data is used, where that data is processed, how we secure that data and how you can update, correct or opt-out that data being used.

Right to provide consent

By agreeing to this Privacy Policy you declare that you are legally a minimum of 13 years of age, and therefore entitled to provide consent under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) for processing of your personal data. At this time we do not provide service to individuals below 13 years of age.

Transfer of data outside of the European Union (EU)

Your personal information may be transferred to and stored at our office and associated data centers. By accepting our Terms of Service and/or a software EULA, you are explicitly consenting to this transfer and storage taking place. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Collection of personal information

We collect your personal information when you purchase our products or services, submit a support ticket or contact us via email. In order to complete purchase of our products or services and in the interests of security, you may be asked to provide your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit/debit card information, business/organisational information (if applicable) and other personal information.

As a provider of Domain registration also known as a "Domain registrar" and SSL certificates, we are required to provide certain information to our trusted 3rd parties in order to provide those services. This may include personal data such as full name, physical address of the customer or business/organisation and telephone number.

The trusted 3rd party of Domain registration will make such information publicly accessible through the use of Domain WHOIS lookups. The trusted 3rd party of SSL certificates will make information such as Organisation Name, Department, Location/City, State/Province and Country available to the public. By purchasing a Domain or SSL certificate the customer agrees that we will transfer his/her personal data to our trusted 3rd party, in order to provide that product or service.

Use of personal information

We will not sell, exchange or transfer your public or private personal information outside of QuickWeb Hosting Solutions (QuickWeb), its associated trading names, trusted partners and 3rd parties without your consent, other than the exceptions listed below.

1\. To process orders of our products and services. Your information is used to verify the legitimacy of the order in the interests of Fraud and Crime prevention. Your information may be temporarily shared with Maxmind, an online fraud prevention provider widely used throughout the web hosting and e-commerce industries. We also use your personal data to process payments and prepare invoices.

2\. To provide technical support and customer service. Your information helps us effectively respond to pre/post sales requests, track existing correspondence and provide technical support for our products and services.

3\. To send account related notifications such as invoices, renewal notifications and cancellation notifications.

4\. To send service related emails such as planned maintenance, service updates, company newsletters and related product or service information.

Processing data

We will process your data for the purpose of providing products or services with the legitimate interest of our business. If data is required for any other purpose, we will first request your consent for any data you provide. If you are unable or refuse to provide personal information, we may be unable to provide our products and services to you. If you opt-out of receiving notifications, you may not be made aware of outstanding payments, service related issues or other changes which may affect the availability or quality of products or services we provide.

Cookies

We use cookies on our billing website (https://secure.quickweb.co.nz), and other control panels you may have access to, in order to assign and track a session to authenticate your web browser to access that service.

We do not use cookies for any other purpose. We do not use cookies to track your activity across unrelated websites and we do not use cookies for advertising or to advise other companies of your activities. If you do not agree with our use of cookies, we are unable to provide service to you.

Log files

Our servers automatically record information in "Log Files" otherwise known as "Application Data", when you visit any of our websites or use our services. This data may include information such as your IP Address, Web Browser, "User-Agent", Operating System, referring web page, session ID, search terms and cookie information. We use this information to diagnose faults and improve the security and availability of our services. With the exception of requests to remove your data as detailed in the proceeding section, any log files will be deleted no later than 12 months after they are written.

Sharing and transfer of Personal information

We will not sell, exchange or transfer your public or private personal information outside of QuickWeb, its associated trading names, trusted partners and 3rd parties without your consent, other than the exceptions listed below.

1\. To process orders of our products and services. Your information is used to verify the legitimacy of the order in the interests of Fraud and Crime prevention. Your information may be temporarily shared with Maxmind, an online fraud prevention provider widely used throughout the web hosting and e-commerce industries. We also use your personal data to process payments and prepare invoices.

2\. To provide technical support and customer service. Your information helps us effectively respond to pre/post sales requests, track existing correspondence and provide technical support for our products and services.

3\. To send account related notifications such as invoices, renewal notifications and cancellation notifications.

4\. To send service related emails such as planned maintenance, service updates, company newsletters and related product or service information.  

Data retention

We retain your personal information for no longer than necessary within the purposes described in this document, or for a period specifically required by law or regulation that we are obligated to follow.

In the event that we are asked to delete or remove personal information, we may retain personal data to the minimum extend necessary, and for as long as necessary to fulfil our legitimate business and contractual requirements. 

After expiration of the retention period, we securely delete, dispose or anonymise your personal information to prevent unauthorised access, loss or theft.

Withdrawing consent (opting out)

If you wish to unsubscribe to receiving information such as periodic emails or notifications, we include unsubscribe information at the end of each email. Alternatively, or if an email is missing unsubscribe information you can email privacy[at]pcsmartgroup.com

You can request that we stop processing your personal data and revoke consent at any time by contacting us with details at the end of this document. 

Access to your personal data

You are responsible for providing current, complete, true and accurate personal information. You are also responsible for maintaining this information, and updating it promptly as necessary to ensure it continues to be current, complete, true and accurate. You can request a change of information by logging into your control panel, or contacting us. 

If you provide information which is not current, complete, true or accurate, or if we have reasonable belief to suspect this information, we have the right to suspend or terminate your products or services with us at any time, and refuse all current and future services.

Protecting your information

We have a number of measures in place to maintain the security and accuracy of your personal information. When placing an order or using our Billing or Support systems, all supplied information is transmitted over End-to-End encryption via Secure Sockets Layer (SSL).

Your rights under the EU GDPR

Under the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) you have the following rights:

The right to be informed.  
The right of access.  
The right to rectification.  
The right to erasure.  
The right to restrict processing.  
The right to data portability.  
The right to object.  
Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling.

Changes to this privacy policy  
If any change is made to this privacy policy, we will notify customers via email.

Questions regarding the information QuickWeb Hosting Solutions has stored about you should be in writing, and addressed to: 

Neodelphi Limited t/a QuickWeb Hosting Solutions  
Suite 5750  
17B Farnham Street  
Parnell  
Auckland 1052  
New Zealand
